Jesús Ruiz

Web Developer and Graphic Designer

I am a Junior Full Stack Developer with 2 years of experience in PHP and Laravel, and basic knowledge of frontend technologies such as JavaScript, React, Astro and NextJS. I have experience in deploying applications on various platforms, which allows me to manage projects comprehensively.

In addition, I have 6 years of experience as a Senior Graphic Designer, specialized in Visual Identity. This combination of skills allows me to contribute in all phases of the project: from the design of visual prototypes, through backend and frontend development, to deployment and maintenance.

△ Visit my portfolio: jesus-portfolio.vercel.app

⊕ I currently reside in Lima, Perú.



Technologies and Skills



Work Experience

Jesuiz Design - Freelancer

2023 - 2024

Graphic Designer & Web Developer

I execute digital solutions in Branding and Web Development internationally. Specifically Corporate Identity Design (Branding), Website Development, Ecommerce and Web Applications.

Clave Publicitaria - Printer's

2022 - 2023

Manager, Graphic Designer & Web Developer

I started as business manager and promoted the integration of new digital services complementing the Printing, Gigantography and Merchandising services.

Geotop - Surveying Company

2021 - 2021

Manager, Marketing Area

I designed all the company's audiovisual material for digital and physical environments. I developed a new Website with Wordpress and optimized all the company's other websites. I managed all the company's graphic design, as well as the edition and transmission of the monthly Webinars.

Techno Global - Printer's

2018 - 2021

Manager, Graphic Designer

I carried out designer activities related mainly to Advertising, Printing and Gigantography. After 6 months I led the advertising activities as Business Manager with 3 people in charge.

Educación

Complete Primary Valera, Trujillo, Venezuela E.B. Eloísa Fonseca

Complete Secondary School

Valera, Trujillo, Venezuela

U.E.C. Juan de Dios Andrade C.P. Ignacio Martín Burk

Graphic Design Technician

2015

Valera, Trujillo, Venezuela

Instuto de Tecnología Industrial Rodolfo Loero Arismendi

Certificados

